A video showing you how to play with the new activities on the treasure page. Hello brothers, I am the sixth grade student of Xiejiao.com.
After a night of exploration, I have thoroughly enjoyed two new activities.
The contents of this video are: Precautions for treasure maps, ways to obtain treasure maps, treasure map locations,
Airdrop location and time, you can jump to the desired content by yourself. Finally, there will be a nine-serve test to test the treasure's explosive rate.
First, here are the things to note about the treasure map.
Be sure to note that the rewards for the same treasure are different for normal and sophisticated treasures.
There are four types of treasure chests: ordinary, high-quality, top-quality, and royal. The treasure map is divided into numbers one to twelve.
Numbers 1 to 7 secretly drawn must be of the highest quality; number 8 must be of the royal family; numbers 9 to 12 must be of the highest quality.
When opening a normal dam, it will be downgraded by one gear. It is recommended to keep it confidential.
Then the same treasure chest can only be opened once, but it can be opened multiple times. It depends on you,
For eight, you can open three boxes of numbers seven, eight, and nine at once, but you cannot open number eight twice.
And it only targets a single cover. For example, if you open No. 6, your teammates can also open No. 6.
Therefore, it is recommended to play with friends and bring a few pictures with you so that you can open them together.
Next is the way to obtain the treasure map. Currently, there are two series of activity pages that can be redeemed with treasure map clues.
In the second series, medicine boxes, airdrop boxes and treasure searches will be produced in the game. The explosion rate is currently very high according to the current test.
Then there are the treasure locations, shown in order: No. 1 is in the underground passage and next to the field supply box.
No. 2 squatted down at the signal tower outside the cement wall, and No. 3 was in the middle of the operating pipeline.
No. 4 is at the container at the back door of the visitor center, and No. 5 is next to the outdoor supplies box on the river beach.
No. 6 is in the field below the small operation, and No. 7 is at the container behind the outbound container position at the top of the dam.
No. 8 is at the innermost part of the container in the administration building. This treasure box will have a red signal, so be careful.
No. 9 is at the container corner on the far right side of the parking wall of the east building; No. 10 is behind the west wall where tourists come down from;
No. 11 is at the pipe gap at the west building construction site; No. 12 is at the gap in the middle of the cement factory.
The last one is the airdrop location and time. The dam now has six fixed airdrop locations, namely the West Building construction site,
The parking wall of the east building, the entrance of the small shop, the bridge head of the river beach, and the fork in the road below the tourists.
And at the supply box next to the broken wall, it was airdropped in Puba for twenty-five minutes.
The Jimmy Bus started landing around twenty-one minutes ago.
It will be the second opening period after the first falling period of two consecutive waves. The current test explosion rate is very high.
Three monkeys appeared in Pubadu. That’s all for the new event. If it helps you,
Please also support Liuliu Sanlian and forward it to your little friends who don’t know the new activities yet!
I wish you all 大红 Seven Treasures in advance.
Finally, let's do a wave of nine consecutive attacks to test and analyze the burst rate. The hardware is three red and one purple.
Liuliu thought it was okay, so he just sent the green message for everyone. Brothers, please go online to Qiuheng!